// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
  {
  numb: 1,
  question: "Our sir teaches Mathematics………………English.",
  answer: "B. besides",
  options: [
    "A. across",
    "B. besides",
    "C. beside",
    "D. both"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 2,
  question: "Please, come………………the bathroom.",
  answer: "A. out of",
  options: [
    "A. out of",
    "B. over",
    "C. on",
    "D. in"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 3,
  question: "Please, don’t laugh……………those beggars.",
  answer: "C. at",
  options: [
    "A. for",
    "B. against",
    "C. at",
    "D. from"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 4,
  question: "Please, stop……..so many mistakes.",
  answer: "C. making",
  options: [
    "A. to make",
    "B. make",
    "C. making",
    "D. makes"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 5,
  question: "She…….her husband for 15 minutes.",
  answer: "B. has been beaten",
  options: [
    "A. is beating",
    "B. has been beaten",
    "C. has been beaten",
    "D. beats"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 6,
  question: "The rain comes……………..the clouds.",
  answer: "D. under",
  options: [
    "A. in",
    "B. near",
    "C. from",
    "D. under"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 7,
  question: "There are…………views on the issue of giving bonus t the employees.",
  answer: "B. divergent",
  options: [
    "A. independent",
    "B. divergent",
    "C. modest",
    "D. adverse"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 8,
  question: "He has………….people visiting him at his house because he fears it will cause discomfort to neighbors",
  answer: "C. stopped",
  options: [
    "A. curtailed",
    "B. requested",
    "C. stopped",
    "D. warned"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 9,
  question: "There is no place for………….in an accountant’s job.",
  answer: "C. errors",
  options: [
    "A. assets",
    "B. asserts",
    "C. errors",
    "D. duffers"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 10,
  question: "Some of the luggage…………..not yet arrived.",
  answer: "A. has",
  options: [
    "A. has",
    "B. have",
    "C. is",
    "D. are"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 11,
  question: "No sooner………..than the police handcuffed him.",
  answer: "C. did he come",
  options: [
    "A. he came",
    "B. did he came",
    "C. did he come",
    "D. had he come"
    
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 12,
  question: "We didn’t……………the programme to be such a huge success.",
  answer: "C. Expect",
  options: [
    "A. Accept",
    "B. Except",
    "C. Expect",
    "D. Access"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 13,
  question: "I suffer from no……………about my capabilities.",
  answer: "A. illusion",
  options: [
    "A. illusion",
    "B. doubts",
    "C. hallucinations",
    "D. imaginations"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 14,
  question: "The student’s aren’t prepared …………….the examination",
  answer: "D. to take",
  options: [
    "A. to give",
    "B. to listen",
    "C. to work",
    "D. to take"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 15,
  question: "Please don’t …………when I am talking.",
  answer: "C. interrupt",
  options: [
    "A. disrupt",
    "B. interface",
    "C. interrupt",
    "D. disturb"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 16,
  question: "It is not fair to cast……………on honest and innocent persons",
  answer: "B. aspersions",
  options: [
    "A. aspiration",
    "B. aspersions",
    "C. Inspiration",
    "D. adulation"
  ]
},
  {
    numb: 17,
    question: "If …………….I would not lose temper",
    answer: "A. I were you",
    options: [
      "A. I were you",
      "B. I was you",
      "C. I am not you",
      "D. I am you"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 18,
  question: "One who hates woman is called………….",
  answer: "D. misogynist",
  options: [
    "A. philanthropist",
    "B. ascetic",
    "C. misogamist",
    "D. misogynist"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 19,
  question: " ……………….takes charge of a prison.",
  answer: "D. A warden",
  options: [
    "A. An editor",
    "B. An optician",
    "C. A detective",
    "D. A warden"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 20,
  question: " Kites………….in future also.",
  answer: "C. will be flown",
  options: [
    "A. fly",
    "B. will fly",
    "C. will be flown",
    "D. will flying"
  ]
},
// you can uncomment the below codes and make duplicate as more as you want to add question
// but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....

//   {
//   numb: 6,
//   question: "Your Question is Here",
//   answer: "Correct answer of the question is here",
//   options: [
//     "Option 1",
//     "option 2",
//     "option 3",
//     "option 4"
//   ]
// },
];